Lowell Thomas
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Lowell Thomas
2.1.3.3.3
Marist College
  Box 1521
- Lowell Thomas, 2.1.3.3.3
  - Lowell Thomas: Lowell Thomas (infant and toddler photographs), 1892 - 1895; 10 (Box 1521)
    - Lowell Jackson, age 5 months, weight 20 pounds; photo made Sept 1892, 1
    - Verso: Lowell Jackson, age 5 months, weight 20 pounds; photo made Sept 1892, 1-verso
    - Lowell Jackson, age 5 months, weight 20 pounds, 2
    - Verso: Lowell Jackson, age 5 months, weight 20 pounds, 2-verso
    - Age 5 mos. [months], weight 20 lbs., 3
    - Verso: Age 5 mos. [months], weight 20 lbs., 3-verso
    - Lowell Thomas, age 7 months; Born April 6, 1892 in Woodington (Darke County), Ohio, 4
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas, age 7 months; Born April 6, 1892 in Woodington (Darke County), Ohio, 4-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas, aged 5-7 months], 5
    - Lowell Thomas Sr. about 9 months, 6
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas Sr. about 9 months, 6-verso
    - Lowell Thomas at 9 months, 7
    - Verso: L.T. at 9 months, 7-verso
    - 3 yrs old [Lowell Thomas standing at right with two other children], 8
    - Verso: 3 yrs old, 8-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas at 3 years of age, standing at right with two other children], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas at 3 years of age, standing at right with two other children], 10
  - Lowell Thomas: Lowell Thomas (childhood photographs), 1900 - 1906; 11 (Box 1521)
    - Caption: L.T., eight years of age [small mounted photograph], 1
    - Lowell Thomas, 8 yrs. old, 2
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas, 8 yrs. Old, 2-verso
    - Lowell Thomas, 8 yrs. old, 3
    - L. T. (on left) at 10 yrs of age, with a friend, 4
    - Verso: L. T. (on left) at 10 yrs of age, with a friend, 4-verso
    - L. T. (on left) at 10 yrs of age, with a friend, 5
    - L. T. with a friend, 10 yrs of age, 6
    - Verso: L. T. with a friend, 10 yrs of age, 6-verso
    - L. T. with a friend, 10 yrs of age, 7
    - Lowell J. Thomas, twelve years old, 8
    - Verso: Lowell J. Thomas, twelve years old, 8-verso
    - Caption: L.T., fourteen years of age [small mounted photographs], 9
    - L.T., 14 yrs. old, 10
    - Verso: LT 14 yrs. old, 10-verso
    - Lowell Thomas, age 14, 11
    - Lowell Thomas as a young boy, 12
    - Lowell Thomas as a young boy, 13
    - Lowell Thomas as a young boy, 14
  - Lowell Thomas: Lowell Thomas (youth photographs), circa 1910; 12 (Box 1521)
    - L.T., age eighteen, 1
    - L.T., age eighteen, 2
    - L.T., age eighteen, 3
    - Note: L.T., age eighteen, 4
    - Young Lowell Thomas, in tuxedo, 5
    - Young Lowell Thomas, in tuxedo, 6
    - Young Lowell Thomas, 7
  - Lowell Thomas: Lowell Thomas (alone), circa 1910s - 1920s; 13 (Box 1521)
    - [Lowell Thomas climbing rock formation], 1
    - How do you like your soldier boy son-in-law? [Lowell Thomas in trench in Europe], 2
    - Verso: How do you like your soldier boy son-in-law?, 2-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas] Age 26 [1918], 3
    - Note: Age 26 [1918], 4
    - [Young Lowell Thomas (before mustache)], 5
  Box 1522
- Lowell Thomas, 2.1.3.3.3
  - Lowell Thomas: Lowell Thomas (alone), circa 1930s; 1 (Box 1522)
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting outdoors] [2 copies], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas with skis], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas (?) in horse pulled sleigh], 3
  - Lowell Thomas: Lowell Thomas (alone), circa 1940s; 2 (Box 1522)
    - Lowell Thomas [2 copies], 1
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas, 1-verso
    - Himself, 2
    - Verso: Himself, 2-verso
    - Lowell Thomas Dean of American Commentators, lecturer and world traveler at the Imperial Hotel, Tokyo, Japan. Mr. Thomas is on an extensive tour of East and South East Asia., 3
    - Verso: FEC-49-4717, 25 July 49, Radio Commentator in Tokyo: Lowell Thomas Dean of American Commentators, lecturer and world traveler at the Imperial Hotel, Tokyo, Japan. Mr. Thomas is on an extensive tour of East and South East Asia. U.S. Army photo - Thomas Please credit U.S. Army photograph; The Department of the Army has no objection to the use of this photograph in commercial advertisements, provide copy and layout are submitted to the REVIEW SECTION PUBLIC INFORMATION DIVISION, DEPARTMENT OF THE ARMY, WASHINGTON D.C., and written permission is obtained, 3-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas reading, sitting in a chair], 4
    - Take to Wash What for? E, 5
    - Verso: "Take to Wash" What for? E, 5-verso
  - Lowell Thomas: Lowell Thomas (alone) [includes color photograph], circa 1950s - 1960s; 3 (Box 1522)
    - [Lowell Thomas], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas with Umbrella] [2 copies], 3
    - by Don Wynn, 170 E. 73rd N.Y. City, 4
    - Verso: by Don Wynn, 170 E. 73rd N.Y. City, 4-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas standing in front of a tree(?)], 5
    - Before starting their protest march they are saying: "Explorers go home!", 6
    - Note: before starting their protest march they are saying: "Explorers go home!", 7
    - Lowell Thomas, March 25, 1960, 8
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas, March 25, 1960, 8-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas] [2 copies], 10
    - Lowell Thomas, 11
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas, 11-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas], 12
    - Caption: Lowell Thomas signature in green ink [6 unsigned copies], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas] [2 copies], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas next to Cog Wheel Route sign], 15
    - [Lowell Thomas at a podium], 16
    - [Lowell Thomas] [2 copies], 17
    - [Lowell Thomas], 18
    - [Lowell Thomas holding up microphone(?) New technology(?)], 19
    - [Lowell Thomas, cut picture], 20
    - [Lowell Thomas] [3 copies], 21
    - [Lowell Thomas with fur jacket and hat.], 22
    - [Lowell Thomas], 23
    - [Lowell Thomas standing in front of a house.], 24
    - [Lowell Thomas standing], 25
    - [Lowell Thomas standing next to sign: No Parking Here] [5 copies], 26
    - [Lowell Thomas with a map behind him.], 27
    - [Lowell Thomas with fur jacket and hat.], 28
  - Lowell Thomas: Lowell Thomas (alone) [includes color photographs], circa 1970s - 1981; 4 (Box 1522)
    - 80th birthday pix, 1
    - Verso: 80th birthday pix, 1-verso
    - Advance for PMs Thursday, 5/13/76. WITH UPI DISPATCH, "THOMAS," BY FRED T. FERGUSON. [?]867404-5/13/76-NEW YORK: It has taken Lowell Thomas 51 years of broadcasting, many more in public speaking, scores of films and 52 books to tell the things he has seen and done from Allenby at Jerusalem and Lawrence in Arabia to Shangrila [sic] and Timbucktu [sic] with thousands of points in between. Thomas is shown during interview with UPI 5/7. In background is a painting of (T. E.) Lawrence in Arabia. UPI (THOMAS) hgr/jl [5 copies], 2
    - Note: Advance for PMs Thursday, 5/13/76. WITH UPI DISPATCH, "THOMAS," BY FRED T. FERGUSON. [?]867404-5/13/76-NEW YORK: It has taken Lowell Thomas 51 years of broadcasting, many more in public speaking, scores of films and 52 books to tell the things he has seen and done from Allenby at Jerusalem and Lawrence in Arabia to Shangrila [sic] and Timbucktu [sic] with thousands of points in between. Thomas is shown during interview with UPI 5/7. In background is a painting of (T. E.) Lawrence in Arabia. UPI (THOMAS) hgr/jl, 3
    - [Lowell Thomas standing at counter], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas with crown in hands], 5
    - I.P.A. [International Platform Association], 1979, 6
    - Verso: I.P.A. [International Platform Association], 1979, 6-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas at podium], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas with microphone], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas in front of Main Top], 9
    - [Porch of house], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with hat in hand], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas (?) on golf cart, golf course (?)], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas with sunglasses], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with hat in hands], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas standing], 15
    - [Lowell Thomas in turtleneck and plaid jacket], 16
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with globe], 17
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with hard hat, construction on ancient monument behind him], 18
  - Lowell Thomas: Lowell Thomas (alone) [color photographs], undated; 5 (Box 1522)
    - LT front door at H Hill [Hammersley Hill], 1
    - Verso: LT front door at H Hill [Hammersley Hill], 1-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas standing in yard], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas leaning on fence], [2 copies], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas wearing fur coat], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas at Walt Disney World podium], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas in front of a map, on set(?)], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas wearing Q.H.C.C. jacket], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas standing at podium], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas standing next to painting, " Lawrence of Arabia"(?)], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas standing next to painting, " Lawrence of Arabia"(?)], 11
    - [Lowell Tomas sitting outside], 12
  - Lowell Thomas: Lowell Thomas (on horseback), circa 1920s -1940s; 6 (Box 1522)
    - [Lowell Thomas on horse rearing up], 1
    - About 1935 [4 copies], 2
    - Verso: about 1935, 2-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas (?) on horseback], 3
    - Lowell Thomas on "Tango" at his farm [2 copies], 4
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas on "Tango" at his farm, 4-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas on horseback, Tango(?)], 5
    - Old Photo, 6
    - Verso: Old Photo, 6-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas(?) riding through a field], 7
    - Riding at C.B. [Clover Brook], 8
    - Verso: Riding at C.B. [Clover Brook], 8-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas(?) on horesback], [4 copies], 9
    - [ Lowell Thomas horseback riding with a companion], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas(?) galloping(?)], [2 copies], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas riding], [5 copies], 12
    - [ Lowell Thomas horseback riding with a companion], [4 copies], 13
  - Lowell Thomas: Lowell Thomas (on horseback), 1967; 7 (Box 1522)
    - Lowell Thomas at Mt. Assiniboine, 1967; # 18 "Saddled Up" by R. H. Coulter, 1
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas at Mt. Assiniboine, 1967; # 18 "Saddled Up" by R. H. Coulter, 1-verso
  - Lowell Thomas: Barbecue, circa 1930s; 8 (Box 1522)
    - [Lowell Thomas in chef's hat on right, Sir Hubert Wilkins in center], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas in chef's hat on right, Viljhalmur Stefansson on left], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas in chef's hat], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas in chef's hat], 4
  - Lowell Thomas: Book signings [Includes color photographs], 1952, circa 1964; 9 (Box 1522)
    - Week of May 12, 1952, 1
    - Verso: Week of May 12, 1952, 1-verso
    - Week of May 12, 1952, 2
    - Verso: Week of May 12, 1952, 2-verso
    - Jim Seward - V.P. CBS in charge of [Arthur] Godfrey, [Edward R.] Murrow and L.T.s, 3
    - Verso: Jim Seward - V.P. CBS in charge of [Arthur] Godfrey, [Edward R.] Murrow and L.T.s, 3-verso
  - Lowell Thomas: Boyhood Home of Lowell Thomas [color photographs], 1970; 10 (Box 1522)
    - Kitchen, cookstove and accessories, 1
    - Verso: Kitchen, cookstove and accessories, 1-verso
    - Kitchen, sugar and flour bin, sink, 2
    - Verso: Kitchen, sugar and flour bin, sink, 2-verso
    - Kitchen, icebox - wall telephone, 3
    - Verso: Kitchen, icebox - wall telephone, 3-verso
    - Kitchen, kitchen china cabinet, 4
    - Verso: Kitchen, kitchen china cabinet, 4-verso
    - Living room, divan and beaded lamp with fringes, 5
    - Verso: Living room, divan and beaded lamp with fringes, 5-verso
    - Dining room, china cabinet, 6
    - Verso: Dining room, china cabinet, 6-verso
    - Dining room, table and sideboard, 7
    - Verso: Dining room, table and sideboard, 7-verso
    - Living room, heating stove in lv. rm. [living room], 8
    - Verso: Living room, heating stove in lv. rm. [living room], 8-verso
    - Living room, piano has 4 pedals, mandolin attachment; piano belongs to the Thomas family, 9
    - Verso: Living room, piano has 4 pedals, mandolin attachment; piano belongs to the Thomas family, 9-verso
    - Study, bookcase made of "Quakies", 10
    - Verso: Study, bookcase made of "Quakies", 10-verso
    - Study, antique loveseat, 11
    - Verso: Study, antique loveseat, 11-verso
    - Study, library table and chair, antique typewriter, 12
    - Verso: Study, library table and chair, antique typewriter, 12-verso
    - Note: Beaver Valley Ranch; Dear Mrs. Nicks, Enclosed are twelve snapshots of the interior of the Boyhood Home of Lowell Thomas. A brief description is written on the back of each picture. I hope these will be helpful in assembling material for the tape. Yours Truly, Ruth Harclerode (Mrs. F. R. Harclerode), 13
  - Lowell Thomas: Broadcasting, 1934; 11 (Box 1522)
    - Caption: Pittsburgh, April 24, 1934, left: Chancellor Bowman, right: Dr. Weidheim Verso: Cathedral of Learning, left: Chancellor Bowman, right: Dr. Weidheim, Pittsburgh - April 24, 1934, 1
    - Verso: Cathedral of Learning Left: Chancellor Bowman Right: Dr. Weidheim Pittsburgh - April 24, 1934, 1-verso
    - Left: Chancellor Bowman Right: Dr. Weidheim Pittsburgh - April 24, 1934, 2
    - Verso: Cathedral of Learning Left: Chancellor Bowman Right: Dr. Weidheim Pittsburgh - April 24, 1934, 2-verso
  - Lowell Thomas: Broadcasting, 1936; 12 (Box 1522)
    - Museum of Bell Laboratories Mar 10, 1936, 1
    - Verso: Museum of Bell Laboratories Mar 10, 1936, 1-verso
    - Sir Wilfred Grenfell and LT, Jany 9, 1936, 2
    - Verso: Sir Wilfred Grenfell and LT, Jany 9, 1936, 2-verso
    - Sir Wilfred Grenfell and LT, Jany 9, 1936, 3
    - Verso: Sir Wilfred Grenfell and LT, Jany 9, 1936, 3-verso
    - Sasha Siemiel [?] lion hunter, Jany 15, 1936 [2 copies] Verso: "Tiger Man" Sascha [sic] Siemel from the Matta Grosso and LT, 4
    - Verso: "Tiger Man" Sascha [sic] Siemel from the Matta Grosso and LT, 4-verso
    - Sasha Siemiel [?] lion hunter [2 copies], 5
    - Note: Sasha Siemiel [?] lion hunter, Jany 15, 1936, 6
    - David Rhys - British Diplomat, 7
    - Verso: David Rhys - British Diplomat, 7-verso
    - Mr. Clayden, Sun Oil, 8
    - Note: Mr. Clayden, Sun Oil, 9
    - Mr. Clayden, Sun Oil, 10
    - Capt. Robert "Bob" Bartlett, exploration, sailing ships, 11
    - Note: Capt. Robert "Bob" Bartlett, exploration, sailing ships, 12
    - I am returning the photograph which I'm sure you will want for your files. Isn't this a picture of Jim Barrett - the other fellow has changed very little, 13
    - Note: I am returning the photograph which I'm sure you will want for your files. Isn't this a picture of Jim Barrett - the other fellow has changed very little, 14
    - [Lowell Thomas interviewing man], 15
    - [Lowell Thomas interviewing man], 16
    - [Lowell Thomas interviewing man], [2 copies], 17
    - [Lowell Thomas interviewing man], 18
    - [Lowell Thomas interviewing man], 19
    - [Lowell Thomas interviewing man], 20
    - [Lowell Thomas interviewing man], 21
  - Lowell Thomas: Broadcasting, circa 1930s; 13 (Box 1522)
    - L.T. and Jimmy Wallington, 1
    - Verso: L.T. and Jimmy Wallington, 1-verso
    - Note: Little photo: Jimmy Wallington, LT's announcer for Literary Digest Verso: LT and Jimmy Wallington, 2
    - [Lowell Thomas with unidentified man], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas(?) with group of men, reviewing broadcat?], 4
    - [audience(?)], 5
  - Lowell Thomas: Broadcasting, circa 1930s - 1940s; 14 (Box 1522)
    - L.T. and George McManus, 1
    - Note: George McManus, creator of "Manny [sic] [Maggie] and Jiggs", 2
    - Geo. McManus, cartoonist Brgin' [Bringing] Up Father, 3
    - Verso: Geo. McManus, cartoonist Brgin' [Bringing] Up Father, 3-verso
  - Lowell Thomas: Broadcasting, 1943; 15 (Box 1522)
    - Mr. Burdette S. Wright, Curtiss-Wright Corporation Vice-President in charge of the Airplane Division; Mr. Lowell Thomas presenting his nightly news commentary on a national network, and Dr. C.C. Furnas, Director of the Curtiss-Wright Research Laboratory [2 copies], 1
    - Verso: 1291-X Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Airplane Division, New York Division, New York State Plants, 20 October, Mr. Burdette S. Wright, Curtiss-Wright Corporation Vice-President in charge of the Airplane Division; Mr. Lowell Thomas presenting his nightly news commentary on a national network, and Dr. C.C. Furnas, Director of the Curtiss-Wright Research Laboratory. Courtesy of Curtiss, Photograph from files of Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Airplane Division, Buffalo, N.Y., Public Relations Department, Neg. no. 1291x, date: Nov. 11 1943, 1-verso
  - Lowell Thomas: Broadcasting, 1945; 16 (Box 1522)
    - [Lowell Thomas at microphone], [6 copies], 1
  - Lowell Thomas: Broadcasting, 1948; 17 (Box 1522)
    - Father and son act, Lowell Thomas, Jr., (left) reports to his famous father on Thomas Senior's nightly radio newscast after returning from an extended trip in Persia. Lowell Junior is following in the exact footsteps of his father, who is radio's oldest newscaster, having started in 1930. The younger Thomas is planning a lecture series based on his voyaging. 12/13/48, 1
    - Note: Father and son act, Lowell Thomas, Jr., (left) reports to his famous father on Thomas Senior's nightly radio newscast after returning from an extended trip in Persia. Lowell Junior is following in the exact footsteps of his father, who is radio's oldest newscaster, having started in 1930. The younger Thomas is planning a lecture series based on his voyaging. 12/13/48, 2
  - Lowell Thomas: Broadcasting, circa 1940s; 18 (Box 1522)
    - L.T.'s program on television, at NBC, 1
    - Verso: L.T.'s program on television, at NBC, 1-verso
    - Note: First TV newscast ever made. Hugh James far left, Charles Warburton, NBC production man beside me Verso: L.T.'s program on Television, at NBC, 2
    - LT's program went out over television for some months, 3
    - Verso: LT's program went out over television for some months, 3-verso
    - Verso: LT was first to put news on television in 1939. This is an example of simulcast; Lowell Thomas 6-40 GOP convention, 4
    - LT was first to put news on television in 1939. This is an example of simulcast; Lowell Thomas 6-40 GOP convention, 4-verso
    - 2 divisions of NBC radio network: WEAF, Red Network; WJZ, Blue Network; later merged, 5
    - Note: 2 divisions of NBC radio network: WEAF, Red Network; WJZ, Blue Network; later merged, 6
    - [Lowell Thomas, far left, with groupof men], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas, far left, with groupof men], 8
  - Lowell Thomas: Broadcasting, circa 1940s; 19 (Box 1522)
    - [Lowell Thomas center with two men around a microphone(?)], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas center with two men around a microphone(?)], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas center with two men around a microphone(?)], 3
    - [hand-colored photograph], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas, on right at microphone with another man, left.], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas at microphone with map behind him], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting at a desk with a map behind him], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting at a desk with a map behind him], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas at microphone, Lowell Thomas, Jr. seated at far left], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas at microphone in front of Pan American World Airways plane], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas 2nd from the left, at microphne with three other men.], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas at the head of the table in front of microphones with a group of men], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas at microphone with another man], [2 copies], 13
    - Lowell Thomas, far right, with a group of men in front of a CBS microphone], [2 copies], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas in background, on the right with a group of men and a woman], [2 copies], 15
    - [Lowell Thomas, on the left with a man and woman in front of CBS microphones], 16
  - Lowell Thomas: Broadcasting, 1950, 1958; 20 (Box 1522)
    - June 1950; LT and Lewis [?] Seaver, Federal Motor Truck Co., Detroit, 1
    - Verso: June 1950; LT and Lewis [?] Seaver, Federal Motor Truck Co., Detroit, 1-verso
    - Lake Placid Club, January 1958, 2
    - Verso: Lake Placid Club, January 1958, 2-verso
  Box 1523
- Lowell Thomas, 2.1.3.3.3
  - Lowell Thomas: Broadcasting [includes 1 color photograph], circa 1960s - 1970s; 1 (Box 1523)
    - Photo by KLZ - RADIO, Denver, Apr 19, 1962, 1
    - Verso: Photo by KLZ - RADIO, Denver, Apr 19, 1962, 1-verso
    - .March 8, 1966, 2
    - Verso: Mar 8, 1966, 2-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas, broadcasting at home(?)], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas in front of a microphone], 4
    - Verso: June 26, 4-verso
    - [contact sheet images of Lowell Thomas at microphone], 5
    - [contact sheet images of Lowell Thomas at microphone], 6
    - [contact sheet images of Lowell Thomas at microphone], 7
    - [contact sheet images of Lowell Thomas at microphone], 8
    - [contact sheet images of Lowell Thomas at microphone], 9
    - [contact sheet images of Lowell Thomas at microphone], 10
    - [contact sheet images of Lowell Thomas at microphone], 11
    - [contact sheet images of Lowell Thomas at microphone], 12
    - [contact sheet images of Lowell Thomas at microphone], 13
    - [contact sheet images of Lowell Thomas standing], 14
    - [contact sheet images of Lowell Thomas standing], 15
    - [contact sheet images of Lowell Thomas standing], 16
    - [contact sheet images of Lowell Thomas standing], 17
    - [contact sheet images of Lowell Thomas standing], 18
    - [contact sheet images of Lowell Thomas standing], 19
    - [contact sheet images of Lowell Thomas standing], 20
    - [contact sheet images of Lowell Thomas standing], 21
    - [contact sheet images of Lowell Thomas standing], 22
    - [contact sheet images of Lowell Thomas standing], 23
  - Lowell Thomas: Broadcasting [final broadcast], 1976 May 16; 2 (Box 1523)
    - NXP1868419-5/15/76-New York: Lowell Thomas signs off for the last time 5/15 as the longest running radio network program goes off the air after 46 years. The familiar "So long until tomorrow" became "So long for now" as Thomas completed his last five-minute news broadcast. The end of his broadcasting career does not mean retirement for Thomas, who is 84. He has written 54 books and has several more planned. UPI, 1
    - Verso: NXP1868419-5/15/76-New York: Lowell Thomas signs off for the last time 5/15 as the longest running radio network program goes off the air after 46 years. The familiar "So long until tomorrow" became "So long for now" as Thomas completed his last five-minute news broadcast. The end of his broadcasting career does not mean retirement for Thomas, who is 84. He has written 54 books and has several more planned. UPI, 1-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas seated at microphone], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas seated at microphone], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas seated at microphone], 4
  - Lowell Thomas: Classmates, 1912; 3 (Box 1523)
    - Caption: Anne Bullen, 1
    - Caption: Mabel Dickerson, 2
    - Caption: Lovingly, Annie McKay Brown, '12, 3
    - Caption: Roger McDonough, 4
    - Caption: Harold F. Trunk, 5
    - Caption: Paul Deeds, "12", 6
    - [male classmate], 7
    - Caption: Edwin Sewell [?], 8
    - Caption: Carl S. Milliken '12, 9
    - Caption: Franny Little, playmate [more illegible], 10
    - Sidney W. Bishop, 11
    - Verso: Sincerely, Sidney W. Bishop, 11-verso
    - Caption: Alice Lind, 12
    - Caption: "George Eddie" Cook, 13
  - Lowell Thomas: Classmates, circa late 1800s; 4 (Box 1523)
    - Caption: Lovingly, Ethel, 1
    - Caption: Donald H.[?] Hoover, 2
    - Caption: Leonard Bowhay - 1912-, 3
    - Caption: Robert R. Nelson, 4
    - Irene Donaldson, 5
    - Verso: Irene Donaldson, 5-verso
    - Caption: Allan Koonce Dray [?], 6
    - Caption: Bamey [Barney?] Sincerely, Florence Carlson E.D.H.S. '13, 7
    - Caption: Bamey [Barney?], 8
    - Verso: E. Biggs E. D., 8-verso
    - Caption: C. Haines Lee '12, 9
    - Caption: Bamey [Barney?], 10
    - Verso: Sincerely, Homer Griffin, 10-verso
    - Caption: Alma Keehu '13 Bamey [Barney?], 11
    - Caption: [?] Richter, 12
    - Caption: Everett H. Parker, 13
    - Caption: Bamey [Barney?], 14
    - Verso: Vance Hefflefinger [?], 14-verso
    - Josephine Zeliff[?], 15
    - Verso: Josephine Zeliff[?], 15-verso
    - Caption: Steere[Steve?] Mathew, 16
    - [female classmate], 17
  - Lowell Thomas: Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, circa late 1800s; 5 (Box 1523)